ELLI RAYNA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 996 7420

elli@elliraynai.com

636 Danforth Ave, Toronto, M4K1R3

in elliraynai

www.elliraynai.com

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with a background in user experience design. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Mongo

NodeJS

Express

Python

Django Git

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive Certificate

General Assembly April 2021 - August 2021

Interaction Design and Development Advanced Diploma

George Brown College September 2018 - April 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Technologist Intern

No Fixed Address | January 2021 - April 2021

- Sole frontend developer on a campaign for a client utilizing the Vue.js framework
- Consistently performed well under pressure amid tight time constraints and had to learn new development skills during the project
- Conducted market research on different types of technologies that could be utilized by clients

AR Designer

Snap | October 2020 - December 2020

- Participated in the Snap AR residency based on the my pitch for a machine learning experience called 'Nourish'
- Responsible for creative direction, user flows, concept designs, motion capture animation for 3D models

Interaction Designer

Cream Productions | May 2020 - August 2020

- Designed and delivered a coherent vision for a casual VR game
- Conducted user interviews, competitive landscape analysis, developing personas
- Built the storyline, mechanics, and levels in collaboration with the development team

Interaction Designer

CFC Media Lab | May 2020 - August 2020

- · Co-wrote, co-produced, co-directed mixed media VR documentary
- Managed team of developers and designers to deliver the artistic vision
- Designed interactions in VR with spatial sound, volumetric capture, and traditional video editing techniques